- 生日快乐 - 生日蛋糕
- Happy Birthday! - Hey, birthday cake!
- 我来了 - 谢谢
- There I am. - Thank you.
真不错
That's nice!
这张拍得不错啊
That's actually a really good one.
有人想吃这个吗
Wait, anybody wants this?
出于同情邀请人家过来 就会变成这样
That's what happens when you do a mercy invite.
我觉得你是想邀请所有人
I believed you wanted to invite everyone.
爸 我不能请了艺术课上的每一个人
Dad, I can't invite everyone in my art class
却不请那个几乎不与其他人来往的人
except for one person without social networking evidence,
我并不想让她更加痛苦
inflicting more pain on that person than was intended.
- 我又不是什么怪物 - 我真为你骄傲
- And I'm not a monster. - I'm proud of you, I think.
她常被留校反省 有时候还会冲老师吼
She gets detention a lot, and she yells at teachers sometimes.
之后有传言说
Then there was that rumor that went around
她不断地离家出走
that she just kept running away from home.
也许她可以叫个优步
Maybe she can Uber.
我真觉得我们现在该回家了
I seriously believe that we can go home now.
是我用词不当让你们觉得这是民主投票吗
Did I mistakenly convey this was a democracy?
等有人来接她了 我们再走
We are not going till she gets picked up.
车抛锚了 我坐公交车回去
The car broke down. I'm just gonna take the bus.
你别坐公交车 我开车送你回去
You're not taking a bus, I'll drive you home.
克莱尔几乎已经攒下了
Claire has almost saved her half of the money
买车需要的一半的钱了 不是吗
she needs for her car. Isn't that right?
这是最后仅有的几次
And this will be one of the few times left
我载你们一程的机会了
I can drive you guys around.
我…
I'm...
你之后就再听不到我爸全程都说着
You won't be able to hear my dad tell jokes that only he thinks
只有他觉得好笑的笑话了 一起来吧
are funny for an entire car ride unless you come.
你不会想错过的
You don't really wanna miss that.
我收到的礼物比我想得要多
I got more gifts than I thought I did.
我能把这个放这里吗
Can I put this in here?
当然 我来 谢谢 玛西亚
Yeah, I'll get it. Thank you, Marcia.
也许他只是喜欢…
Maybe he just is into...
也许他只是安于现状而已
Maybe he's just content where he... where he is.
要帮忙吗
Can I help you?
什么
What?
要是他的话 他非常… 他真的很有意思
If this is the one, he's so... he's really funny.
- 他每周都会录这种视频 - 这简直…
- He does these weekly videos. - This is...
- 看见没 - 太随性了 太诡异了
- See? - It's so random. It's so weird.
- 你肯定是喜欢上他了 - 暂停
- Yeah, you have a crush on him. - Pause it.
我不懂 倒回去
I don't get it. Yeah, go back.
- 你怎么会不懂呢 - 我就是不懂
- Why don't you get it? - I just don't get it.
他肤白貌美又金发 太可爱了
It's like, he's blond, and he's cute.
不 他的眉毛实在是…
No, his eyebrows are just like...
瞎说 他的眉毛
Shut up. His eyebrows?
- 你欣赏不来他的眉毛 - 没错
- That's the one thing you couldn't get? - Yeah!
但我就是被眉毛撩到了
I get turned on by eyebrows, though.
好吧 太逗了
Okay, that's funny, yeah.
- 你看他干了什么 - 他怎么能那么做
- You see what he does, though? - How does he even do that?
我给你看视频就是为了这个
That's the whole point why I'm showing you.
- 太赞了 - 太厉害了
- It's so genius. - So bad.
抱歉 先生 我想你上错车了
Pardon me, sir. I think you have the wrong car.
分裂
我们醒来就在这了
We woke up in here.
发生了什么
What the hell is going on?
我们为什么在这里 我爸出什么事了
What are we doing here? What happened to my dad?
他在外面
He's out there.
你知道我爸出什么事了吗
Do you know what happened to my dad?
我第一个选你
I choose you first.
只要一会儿就好
It's only gonna be a minute.
尿自己身上 尿自己身上
Pee on yourself. Pee on yourself.
不 不
No! No!
不
No!
不要
Don't!
不
No!
把门打开
Open the door!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
他要我给他跳舞
He wanted me to dance for him.
外面的门锁上了
The outside door is locked.
一切都没事
Everything is okay.
我们没事
We're okay.
我听见水花轻轻溅起的声音
I hear the tiniest little splash.
它过来了
And here it comes.
自然界中罕有 就像这样
A freak of nature, like this.
他穿过小河 他是如此的高
So, he comes across the stream, and he's so tall,
水连他的肚子都淹不到
that the water doesn't even get to his belly.
接着他停下了
Then he stops.
我的心脏都要跳出来了
And my heart's coming out of my chest.
你第一次猎鹿所以紧张了
You got buck fever.
约翰叔叔紧张了
Uncle John's got buck fever.
才不是的 凯茜 你爸是个骗子
That's not true, Casey. Your daddy's a liar.
- 那鹿角有多大 - 巨大无比
- How big was the rack? - It was huge.
射击的时候你应该看着哪里 凯茜
Where are you supposed to look when you shoot, Casey?
看着躯干
At the body.
那他为什么却看着鹿角
Then why was he looking at the rack?
因为他第一次猎鹿紧张了
'Cause he had buck fever.
你说什么她就跟着学什么
She'll say anything you say.
等三年后
You gonna do that
你拿到狩猎许可证 你第一次猎鹿也会紧张吗
when you get your mentored hunting license in three years?
不会 先生
No, sir.
吃完以后记得把手套戴上
Be sure you put your gloves on after you finish.
在外面手脚是最先挨冻的
Your feet and your hands get cold first out there.
突发新闻 绑架
三名学生被绑架
Three students abducted.
一名学生的父亲在普鲁士国王商场
The father of one of the students
晕头转向地醒来 报道称他被下了药
woke up dazed in King of Prussia, reportedly drugged.
他发现孩子和车都已失踪
He found the kids and the car missing.
有任何线索 请联系当地警察
邻居们均表示怀疑
Neighbors are in disbelief.
平素安静的社区因绑架案而震惊
A normally quiet community is reeling after this abduction.
如果你知道这些女孩的下落
If you any information concerning the whereabouts of these girls
请立即联系警方
you are urged to contact the police.
巴里: 我要见你 急事
你打开那扇门也没有用 克莱尔
It doesn't matter if you open that door, Claire.
外面还有一扇锁着的门
There's a second locked door.
他随时会再进来的
He's gonna come in here again any second,
我们不能再让他带走我们中的一个
and we're not letting him take one of us out again.
我们只是挣扎尖叫
We just... we just cried and screamed,
我们没有伤害他是因为我们怕激怒他
and we didn't hurt him because we were afraid to get him upset.
天哪 都是受害者无能的表现
God, that's victim shit! Jesus!
我们应该跟他打
We should fight him.
我们要对他拳打脚踢
We should drop a crazy-ass bomb on him.
我看见他扛着你们其中一个
I saw him carry one of you and lay you on the bed
毫不费力地放在床上
like you weighed nothing.
他一拳就能把我们打昏
One punch from him would knock one of us out.
我上过六个月的美式空手道课
I took... I took six months of Kenpo karate class.
你弄疼攻击者来分散他的注意力
And you distract the assailant with pain.
在你们眼中一切都这么容易
Everything is so easy for you guys.
你做一个动作 还能预测到接下来会发生什么
You do one thing, you can predict the next thing.
这种情况下 这办法行不通的
It's not the way it's gonna be in this situation.
我们逃不出去的
We're not getting out of here!
你的意思是 你不打算全力一搏吗
You're saying that you're not gonna fight with everything in you?
唯一的机会…
You know, the only chance...
我们唯一的机会
The only chance we have
就是我们三个一起和他拼了
is if all three of us go crazy on this guy.
我们得赶紧行动
We have to hurry.
我们需要你 凯茜
We need you, Casey.
克莱尔很聪明的 我们就听她的吧
Claire is smart, let's listen to her.
假如你愿意动手 那我也加入
I'll do it if you're gonna do it, too.
- 我们能拼得过他 - 他会伤害我们
- We can win. - He'll hurt us.
不 你们两个都闭嘴
No. Shut up, both of you.
你振作一点
You're gonna pick your miserable self up
帮我们逃出这里
and help us get out of here.
你算了吧
Blow me.
你在普鲁士国王商场
And your six months of karate
上的六个月的空手道课也算了吧
at the King of Prussia Mall can blow me, too.
不不 你今天不能这样
No. No, no, you-you can't do this today.
你现在不能这样
You can't do this right now.
你为什么要这样 你为什么这副德行
Why do you do this! Why do you act like this?
为什么你一副与你无关的样子
Why do act like you're not one of us?
凯茜 在瞄准的时候…
When you aiming, Casey...
要把两只眼睛都睁开
Always keep both eyes open.
用枪管指着你的猎物
Cover your target with the barrel,
然后枪跟着猎物走 掌握它的节奏
then move with it to get its pace.
提醒你 头几次会很挫败
I'm warning you its gonna be frustrating the first times.
你会射不到它或者射太过
You're gonna shoot under it or behind it.
你要学会如何紧跟目标
You'll learn to stay with it.
雌性比雄性要聪明
Females are smarter than the males,
这点你是清楚的 因为就和人类一样
but you know that, it's like humans.
雌性的嗅觉是保命的关键
Females use their nose to stay alive.
确保它们有掩护
They make sure they have cover.
她们总是牢记 自己要努力活下来
They always remember, they're trying to stay alive.
公鹿会发出声响暴露位置
Bucks go off by themselves.
在交配季节公鹿会变傻
Bucks get dumb during mating season.
男孩子们总是太吵了
Boys make too much noise.
没错
Yes, they do.
我比男孩子厉害 是不是
I'm better than a boy, right?
没错
Yes, you are.
等你们说的话有意义时 我会出声的
I'll let you know when I hear something that makes sense.
我们甚至都不清楚 目前这是什么情况
We don't even know what this is yet.
我有了灵感
I... I was inspired.
不 不 不 那张
N-n-n-no, that one.
粉色带刺双排扣长礼服之前那个
That one, before the pink frock coat with the thorns.
那个本来应该弄成…
That's supposed to be like a...
弄成贴身夹克那种
like a tailored jacket,
但我要用手给它印上报纸大字标题
but I'm gonna hand-print it with newspaper headlines.
我是个穿衣简单的人
Well, I'm a simple blouse-and-skirt person,
但这些…
but these...
这些真是太艺术了 巴里
these are very artistic, Barry.
这正是那种
Just the kind of thing
汉普敦[富人区]的女士们会花一万五千美元
Hamptons ladies would spend 15,000 dollars on
就为了在慈善晚宴上穿一次的衣服
to wear once at a charity ball.
别说啦
Shut up.
你知道的 我不能待太久
You know, I-I can't stay too long.
我就是来拜访一下
This is... this is just a... just a visit.
告诉我发生什么事了
Well, tell me what's going on?
什么 你指那封邮件吗
What? You mean the email?
没什么特别的
It's just the usual things.
就是感觉有点不堪重负了
Just feelings of being overwhelmed.
你的邮件写得太简洁了
Well, the terseness of your email
让我感觉事情挺紧迫的
made it sound specific and time-related.
你是在找什么吗
Are... are you looking for something?
- 没有 我只是在… - 没有吗
- No. No, I'm just... - No?
只是在欣赏而已
Just admiring.
- 我现在好多了 - 工作如何
- I'm better now. - How's work?
- 棒极了 - 我上次和他们谈的时候
- It's great! - Well, when I last spoke to them,
他们说你是个模范员工
they believed you were a model employee.
他们觉得你又细致又认真
They found you meticulous and conscientious.
- 你知道的吧 - 我知道
- You know this, right? - I do.
你已经管理了那地方10年了
You've managed there for ten years.
你尽忠职守 巴里
You're functioning very well, Barry.
对你而言 那里是个难得的好单位
And it's a rare and wonderful place for you to work.
的确如此
Yes, it is.
其他有你这种心理障碍的病人中
You know, of all my other clients with your disorder,
你是工作最稳定的一个
you've been the most consistent at your job.
发生什么事了吗 巴里
Did something happen, Barry?
你多大年纪了
How old are you?
网上对于这问题的答案不太一致
Just the internet is inconsistent on this point.
你为什么想到问这个
Why is that on your mind?
你退休或者去世之后 谁来照顾我们
Who's gonna look after us when you retire or pass on?
我们将不得不自己照顾自己
You know, we're gonna have to take care of ourselves
别人甚至都不相信我们的存在
and nobody even believes that we exist.
假如我出事了
If ever something were to happen to me,
我安排了
I've made arrangements
巴尔的摩的一名同事接手
with a colleague from Baltimore to take over.
你… 你是一个人住吗
You... you live alone?
你知道的
You know this.
抱歉 我是想问你独居多久了
I'm sorry, I just meant how long?
一直如此
Always.
那一定很孤独吧
That must be so lonely.
你猜怎么着 我… 我感觉好多了
You know what, I'm... I'm doing much better.
我不该给你发邮件的
I-I shouldn't have emailed you.
我只是… 瞧瞧我 我太冲动了
I'm-I'm just... Look at me, I'm too impulsive.
顺便一问 有人听你的吗
By the way, is anybody listening?
有人在乎我们吗
Does anybody care about us?
有的 实际上巴黎大学
Yes, the University of Paris
还邀请我去做讲座呢
has asked me to do a lecture, in fact.
我会用网络视频 在这里做讲座
I'm going to be doing it via Skype from right here.
人们越来越相信了
People are believing more.
我们下周老时间见
Let's meet at our usual time next week.
我希望你先别走 巴里
I would rather you didn't leave, Barry.
发生什么事了吗
Did something happen?
别担心 我只是来看看你
Don't worry, this was just a visit.
我现在感觉好多了
I'm doing much better. I actually...
你的素描不要了吗 巴里
Don't you want your sketches, Barry?
平时你对它们可是宝贝得很
You're usually very protective of them.
对哦 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
我们下周老时间见
I'll see you next week at our usual time.
谢谢你为我们抗争 弗莱彻医生
Thanks for fighting for us, Dr. Fletcher.
- 谢谢你 弗莱彻医生 - 不客气
- Thanks, Dr. Fletcher. - Welcome.
我觉得我会搞砸的
I just think I'm gonna blow it.
不会的 会顺利的
No, you'll be great.
- 我们下周见 - 好的 谢谢
- I'll see you next week. - Okay, thank you.
我不明白你是怎么和这些人打交道的
I don't know how you work with those people.
- 和哪些人 - 你的病人们
- What people? - Your patients.
你不能用拇指去转轮子 傻子
You can't use your thumbs to spin the wheel, dumbasses!
他们总是用拇指
They always use their thumbs.
我们将这些
W-well, we look at people
曾受过重大打击 与众不同的人视作有缺陷
who've been shattered and different as less than.
如果他们反而比我们更健全呢
What if... they are more than us?
什么
What?
你相信他们吗 你的病人
You believe them? Your patients?
就我们两个人私下说说
You know, just between you and me.
我相信
Yes, I do.
轻轻地拨 轻轻地拨
Flick it! Flick it!
- 无意冒犯 我反正不信 - 没关系
- I don't believe it. No offense. - No.
只要您打电话
But when you call,
我们就再免费送您一台脚轻松
we'll send you a second Easyfeet absolutely free.
脚轻松
只需再多加一点点手续费
Just pay separate processing.
您能得到两台脚轻松
So that's two easyfeet...
就那个 我得买那个
That! I need to buy that.
限时优惠不等人
This young offer won't last...
- 他回来了 - 外面有位女士
- He's back. - There's a lady outside.
丹尼斯 承认你的所作所为吧
Dennis, admit what you've done.
别生气
Don't get upset.
可别告诉我
Don't tell me.
我有点害怕了
I'm getting frightened.
我还以为你能控制局面
I thought that you had this under control.
- 请告诉我为时未晚 - 食物准备好了
- Please tell me it's not too late. - The food is waiting.
她在那间房里吗
Is she in that room?
- 我们在这儿 - 救救我们
- We are here! - Help us!
我们在这里面
We are in here!
丹尼斯 这什么情况 有多少个人
Dennis, what is this? How many are there?
别别 别进去 别进去
N-n-no... don't go in there! Don't go in there!
别担心
Don't worry.
我会和他谈谈
I'll talk to him.
他听我的话
He listens to me.
他不太舒服
He's not well.
他知道你们来这里的意义
He knows what you're here for.
我不准他碰你们
He's not allowed to touch you.
他知道的
He knows that.
病患编号 600-650
- 卡伦 - 乔
- Karen. - Joe.
他们说你不能在全国学术会上
They said you can't have your own panel
主持研讨小组
at the national conference.
不过他们还是妥协了
They conceded, however,
你可以参加情感障碍研讨会
that you can be part of the mood disorder panel.
这不是一种情感障碍
It's not a mood disorder.
我知道你的观念 卡伦
I'm aware your beliefs, Karen.
这次有了新的证据 他们能接受吗
Well, were they open this time with the new evidence?
你竟然用狗做为证据之一
One of your arguments is a dog?
你竟然提交了一个视频 其中一条狗
You submitted video of a dog acting differently
在不同的时间对你的一名病人作出不同的反应
to one of your patients at different time?
比那还要更激动人心
It is more dramatic than that.
他们成为了自己认为的人
They are what they believe they are.
他们的大脑学会了自我保护
The brain has learned to defend itself.
你每次提起他们 都把他们说得神乎其神
You speak of them like they're supernaturally gifted.
好像他们拥有超能力之类的
Like... like they have powers or something.
卡伦 他们都是病人 遭受过创伤
Karen, these are patients. They have been through trauma.
或许现在他们能够做到我们做不到的事情
And perhaps now they're capable of something we're not.
我们现在有脑部扫描技术
We have brain scans now.
分离性身份识别障碍[多重人格]患者
DID patients have changed
利用思想改变了自己的人体化学机能
their body chemistry with their thoughts.
他只是想吓吓我们而已
He's just trying to scare us.
他完全可以和自己交流
He was having a full conversation with himself.
"食物准备好了"那句话是什么意思
What was that line about "the food is waiting"?
你们知道的吧 这越来越累人了
Does everyone get how whacked this is
我们得马上逃出去
and that we need to get out of here now?
你们… 不
You... no.
请保持卫生
Please keep your area neat.
这个卫生间惨不忍睹
The bathroom is unacceptable.
为了便于你们区分
To make it easy,
我用颜色标记了 蓝瓶用来擦地板
I-I've color-coded this. Use the blue bottle for the floor.
粉瓶用来擦瓷砖
And the pink bottle for ceramic surfaces.
帕特里夏提醒了我
Patricia has reminded me that...
我被派去抓你们是有原因的
I was sent to get you for a reason.
你们是圣食
That you are sacred food.
我保证不会再打扰你们了
And I promise not to bother you again.
或许他养了条狗之类的
Maybe he has a dog or something.
他会把我们喂给狗吃
Think he's gonna feed us to his dogs?
病患编号 617: 帕特里夏 11/23
病患编号 617: 丹尼斯 8/23
病患编号 617: 黑德维希 9/23
凯茜
Casey.
Casey!
我叫黑德维希 我有红袜子
My name is Hedwig. I have red socks.
他在行动
He's on the move.
什么
What?
他 在
He's... on...
行 动
the... move.
- 谁 - 有人要来找你们了
- Who? - Someone's coming for you.
你们可不会乐意他来的
And you're not gonna like it.
你们在睡觉的时候有点吵
You guys make noises in your sleep.
- 告诉我们 - 我不应该说
- Tell us. - I'm not supposed to say.
但是 他对人们做了一些可怕的事情
But he's done awful things to people.
他也会同样这么对你们
And he'll do awful things to you.
- 我还有蓝袜子 - 我们是他的食物吗
- I have blue socks, too. - We're his food?
- 你几岁了 - 九岁
- How old are you? - Nine.
所以你不是劫持我们的那个家伙
So you're not the guy that took us?
- 不是 - 你也不是那位女士
- No. - You're not the lady?
你是瞎了吗
What are you, blind?
你不知道他们是如何思考的
You don't know how they think?
不知道 他们… 他们只告诉我一点点
No, they don't, they don't tell me much.
我刚吃了个热狗
I just ate a hotdog.
你能帮帮我们吗 黑德维希
Could you help us, Hedwig?
不能 我… 我都不应该出现在这里
No. I'm.... I'm not even supposed to be here.
我把表现机会从丹尼斯先生那儿偷过来
I stole a light from Mr. Dennis,
但他马上就要回来了
but he'll be back real soon, and...
我不能把表现机会抢过去太久
I can't steal a light for too long
否则他发现了就会生气之类的
or he'll know and get angry, etc.
- 再见啦 - 等等
- See ya! - Wait!
我们听到了些事情
We heard something.
我们之前不明白
We didn't understand it,
但现在知道了
but... now we do.
你知道我们听到什么了吗
Do you know what we heard?
你们听到什么了
What did you hear?
过来
Come here.
我悄悄告诉你
I'll whisper it to you.
那好吧
Okay.
这个人…
This guy...
是冲着你来的
is coming for you.
- 你个大骗子 - 我从不说谎 黑德维希
- You're a big fibber. - I never lie, Hedwig.
但是 丹尼斯先生…
But... but Mr. Dennis..
他说他跟踪了那两个女孩四天
He said that he followed those two girls for four days
他知道 他要找的就是她们俩
and that he knew that they were the ones that he would want.
你不在的时候
When you're not around,
丹尼斯和那位女士说过了
Dennis and the lady talked about it.
他们说这次他很想找个男孩
They talk about how he wants a boy this time.
他们会把你给他
They're going to give him you.
不 帕特里夏女士 她说…
No, Ms. Patricia, she said...
她说 她不再生我的气了
She said she's not mad at me anymore.
她有时候还会唱歌给我听
She sings to me sometimes.
我觉得帕特里夏女士还是有点生你的气
I think Ms. Patricia's still a little mad at you.
帕特里夏女士觉得我… 觉得我很笨
Ms. Patricia thinks I'm... She thinks I'm stupid.
她觉得我会犯一些愚蠢的错误
She thinks I make silly mistakes.
看着我
Look at me,
我们就像是你的保姆
we're like your babysitters.
我会让你看电视 给你做饭
I'll let you watch TV and make you a fun dinner.
我们都得离开这里
We all need to get out of here.
你可以带我们出去
You could show us the way out.
有人回来之前 我们就已经出去了 但是…
We could be gone before anybody gets back, but...
我们得快点 黑德维希
we have to hurry, Hedwig.
我们得快点离开这里
We have to hurry and get out of here.
等… 等一下
Wait, wait a minute.
在不让在这工作的麻烦精发现的情况下
It took forever to get this place safe
把这个地方改造得很安全花了很长时间
without the nosey bodies that work here finding out.
你们不能出去
You can't get out of here!
- 我得去擤鼻涕了 - 不 拜托不要走
- I have to blow my nose. - No, no, wait, please don't go!
谁来了
Who's coming?
- 这真的很吓人 - 没人来
- This is seriously scary. - No one is coming.
他说了点什么
He said something.
他说了什么关于让这个房间安全的事
He said something about making the room safe.
这都是全新的石膏板
This is all new drywall.
不安全的是什么
What was unsafe?
等一下 确定要这么做吗
Wait, are we sure about this?
凯茜 你说得对
Casey, you're right.
这里的确有点什么
There's something in here.
他是在掩盖出去的路
He was covering up a way out.
看到他就告诉我
Tell me if you see him.
凯茜 告诉我们你看到了什么
Casey, tell us what you see!
他来了
He's here.
不能让他进来
You can't let him in!
别让他进来 这是我们唯一的机会了
You can't let him in! This is our one chance.
- 我们成功不了的 - 能成功的
- We're not gonna make it. - Yes, we are!
什么 你们在做什么
What... Hey, what are you guys doing?
好了
Okay, okay, quit it.
别闹了
Okay, guys?
让我进去
Let me... can you let me in?
等一下 我们在换衣服
Give us a second, we are changing.
你们在干什么
What are you guys doing?
让我进去
Let me in!
这一点也不好笑
Guys, you're not being funny.
你们现在的行为太贱了 我要抽你们耳光
You're being bithes. Now, I'm gonna slap you!
我要抽你们…
I'm gonna slap you in your face and your...
求你们帮我拖住他
Just give me as much time as you can.
你们会让我惹上麻烦的
You're gonna get me into trouble.
伙计们
Guys!
玛西亚
Marcia.
我还以为我弄丢你了
I thought I lost you.
请你出来 好吗
Would you... would you step outside, please?
你喜欢嘲笑我们
You like to make fun of us,
但是我们比你想的要强大
but we're more powerful than you think.
出来
Step outside.
请
Please.
你不应该骗小孩
You shouldn't trick children.
那显示出你是什么样的人
That shows who you are.
看看你的毛衣 太破了 太脏了
Look at your sweater. It's- it's ruined, it's dirty.
脱下来
Remove it.
我在努力做个好人
I'm trying to be good.
你们不会再看到你们的朋友了
You'll not see your friend again.
她被单独关起来了
She'll be kept separate.
现在把你们的裙子和上衣脱下来
Now, take off your skirt and take off your shirt.
你们的衣服都沾了灰尘弄脏了
Your clothes, you got all dirty from the dust.
一个分离性身份识别障碍患者的
One identity in an individual
其中一重人格
with dissociative identity disorder
可能有高胆固醇 就那一重人格
can have high cholesterol. One.
有过这样的案例
There are been cases where one identity
有一重人格对蜂螫过敏
is allergic to bee stings.
其他的人格却不
The others are not.
存不存在某些时刻
Are there moments where two identities
两种人格共存
can co-exist at the same time?
的确有时候 两种人格
There are times when two identities
可以同时获得表现机会[光]
can take the light or the spot,
或称聚焦 或称意识
or consciousness at the same time.
这在我研究的一名学生身上出现过
This happened with a student that I was working with.
她的左右手同时
And her left and right hands were taking notes
用不同的笔迹
in different hand-writings
对不同的事情记笔记
about separate things at the same time.
人格之间的差别可能是很大的
The differences in the identities can be dramatic.
就像你我之间
As much as the difference between you and me
会堂里每个人的差别一样大
and every person in that auditorium.
不同的人格有不同的智商
The identities have different IQs.
有不同的体力
They have different physical strengths.
一种人格是个俄罗斯举重运动员
One personality is a Russian weightlifter,
能举起是他自身体重三倍的东西
and can lift three times his body weight.
他们高度集中的能力
Their ability to hyper-focus
和他们不同的经历令人震惊
and have different experiences is astounding.
这些人是因为他们的苦难
Have these individuals through their suffering
激发了大脑的潜力吗
unlocked the potential of the brain?
这是通往
Is this the ultimate doorway
所有我们称之为未知的终极之门吗
to all things we called unknown?
这是我们超自然意识的来源吗
Is this where our sense of the supernatural comes from?
是关于色彩浓度
It's about depth and...
和曲线的 你看到那个了吗
and curves. And, hey, you see that one?
有点像雪尼尔纱针织连衣裙
It's kinda like a chenille sweater-dress.
你是谁
Who are you?
巴里
Barry.
我觉得你不是巴里
I don't think you are.
我开发出了一种"嗅觉"
I've developed a nose for sensing
能够判断我在和谁说话 没有和谁说话
whom I'm talking to and whom I'm not.
是我做了什么吗
Have I done something?
你已经连续两天发邮件进行临时预约了
You've emailed for an unscheduled appointment two days in a row.
我们只是觉得不堪重负 我有一堆问题
We're just feeling overwhelmed, I... garden-variety of issues.
我认为是奥威尔 杰德
I think Orwell, or Jade,
塞缪尔或海因里奇
or Samuel or Heinrich
短暂得到了表现机会并给我发了邮件
had the light for a moment and emailed me.
你却来这儿告诉我一切都好
And you're here to tell me everything is okay.
是我给你发的邮件
I emailed you.
我能和他们之一谈一谈吗
May I talk to one of them, please?
不能
That can't happen.
我告诉他们
I told them
今天我想单独与你进行心理诊疗
that I wanna spend the session with you today.
我再问一遍
I'm gonna ask again.
现在和我交谈的是谁
To whom am I speaking with now?
弗莱彻医生 我是巴里
Dr. Fletcher, it's Barry.
并不像巴里 巴里是外向的领导者
It doesn't seem like Barry. Barry is an extroverted leader.
我就是啊
Of course, I am.
我从专业角度猜一下
I'm gonna take a professional guess
根据我从巴里口中得知的
based on the description of all 23 identities
在凯文体内的全部23种人格的描述
that live in Kevin's body that I've gotten from Barry.
我猜你是丹尼斯
I think I'm talking to Dennis.
不过由于某些原因 他被禁止出现
But he's been banned from the light because, among other reasons,
他喜欢看年轻姑娘裸体跳舞
He has a proclivity to watch young girls dance naked,
他自己也知道这样不对
which he himself knows it's wrong
他自己也做过抗争 但没什么成效
and he's fought against it with little success.
我很高兴我们终于能见面
I'm encouraged we can finally meet.
我之所以这么猜
And I've guessed this
是因为你进来之后
because you've adjusted the chocolate dish twice
动了两次巧克力碟子 我知道你有强迫症
since you came in here and I understand you have OCD.
我知道了 我知道了 聪明
Now I see, now I see. That's clever.
聪明 但我不是丹尼斯
That's clever. But I'm not Dennis.
你和帕特里夏
And you and Patricia
已经有很长一段时间被禁止出现了
have been banned from the light for quite a while now.
最主要的原因应该是你们的信仰
Primarily, shall we say, because of your beliefs.
帕特里夏和丹尼斯很不稳定 我不是丹尼斯
Patricia and Dennis are very unstable. I'm not Dennis.
你们俩现在都是主导吗
Have you both take in charge now?
请相信我 我是巴里
Please believe me, I'm Barry.
请原谅我 我的职责就是质疑你
You must forgive me, my job is to challenge you.
你现在肯定也知道了 我已经知道了
And as you must know by now, I have plenty of opinions
你们每个人格是如何生活的
about how everyone should live their lives.
问我关于时尚的事 我可以证明的
Ask me something about fashion, I'll prove it.
或者… 你看你看 瑞士莲巧克力
Or... or I'll... Look, look, look. Lindt.
你看看
Yeah, you look.
你看 我不是丹尼斯
You see, I'm not Dennis.
还要我做别的事吗
You want me to do something else?
你有冰淇淋吗 反正这衣服是混棉的
You got ice cream? This shirt is cotton blend anyway,
这领子是三个流行季以前的样式
and the collar is from three seasons ago.
围脖领 别逗了
Snood? I mean, come on.
杰 你从哪家"健康"的快餐店
Jai, what health-conscious fast food purveyor
买来这些鸡翅
did you originally solicit to buy these chicken wings
还以一种轻微自杀姿态又热了一遍
you've so lovingly reheated in a minor suicidal gesture?
猫头鹰餐厅
Hooters.
总不能把它们扔了吧 弗莱彻医生
And you can't just threw them out, Dr. Fletcher.
这简直大错特错
This is wrong on so many levels.
3点15分的已经看完了 看看3点18分左右的
We finished about 3:15, so look around 3:18.
你肚子上长了肉 杰
You're getting a little soft on the middle, Jai.
快餐店创始人利用我们对脂肪无穷无尽的需求
The authors of Hooters play on our incessant need for fat
还利用了男人总想接近隆过胸的女人的需求
and man's incessant need to be in the proximity of augmented breasts.
这就像亨利五世开了家快餐店一样
It's like Henry V ran a fast food franchise.
- 那家店挺不错的 弗莱彻医生 - 好吧
- It's a good place, Dr. Fletcher. - Right.
你怎么知道垃圾会洒一地
How'd you know the trash would be spilled?
怎么说呢 杰
How can I say this, Jai.
可能是因为你不够细心吧
You're not the most meticulous of people.
这人不太讲究啊
This guys isn't very neat, is he?
就这样穿过了垃圾堆
He walked right through the trash.
的确 任何一个正常人都会绕着走
No, Jai. Any normal person would've walked around it.
这是装出来的
That was an act.
你想干什么 丹尼斯
What are your up to, Dennis?
还是说做主的是帕特里夏
Or is it Patricia who's deciding things?
我们不会死的
We're not gonna die.
虽然坏事常发生
Bad things happen.
但不会像这样
But not like this.
凯茜
Casey.
跟我说说话
Talk to me.
我们得找到窗户或者门什么的吗
We need to get to a window or a door or something.
不是吗
Don't you think?
刺激 凯茜 在于你能不能做到
The thrill, Casey, is about whether you can
比这动物更聪明
or can't outsmart this animal.
你之前都不喜欢来这里
See, you didn't used to like to come out here.
这像是我们的家庭传统一样 对吧
This is like our family tradition, right?
- 这一枪真漂亮 兄弟 - 谢谢 约翰
- Good shot, big brother. - Thank you, John.
我给你送饭来了 贪睡鬼
I have your meal, sleepyhead.
吃吧
Eat.
好吃吗 里面放了辣椒
It's good? It's got paprika in it.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我要把一支很漂亮的花戴在你头上
I think I'll put a pretty flower in your hair.
好了
Here we are.
这是为了表示你们很重要
That's to show how important you are.
跟我来 我们好好吃一顿饭
Come along. And we'll have a proper meal.
我明白你们对这一切很不满意
I understand, these must all seem so unsatisfactory for you.
不过我们已经尽力了
But we are doing the best we can.
好吃吗
Good?
克莱尔能来跟我们一起吃吗
Can Claire come eat with us?
恐怕不行
No, no, I'm afraid that can't happen.
她差点毁了我们隆重的招待会
She almost ruined our big reception.
我听说亚洲音乐有助于消化
I've heard that Asian people's music aids digestion.
我再给你们做一个三明治
I'll make you a second sandwich.
你们知不知道
Do you know...
狮子一家一天能吃15千克食物
a family of lions can eat 35 pounds a day?
一头雄鹿会在繁殖期
A buck can loose 30% of its weight
因为追逐母鹿 体重降低30%
during mating season chasing does round.
它们是晨昏性动物
They're crepuscular, right?
意味着它们在黄昏或破晓间活动 你真聪明
Means they travel around during dusk and dawn. Good for you.
切歪了
It's crooked.
抱歉
I... Forgive me.
我不知道你们知不知道
I don't know if you know,
老虎只有三十颗牙齿
but tigers have only 30 teeth.
比狗还少十二颗
That's 12 less than a dog.
我觉得这很有趣
I thought that was a fun fact.
不
No.
回房间 关上门 快去
Go to your room, shut the door. Do it now.
"日光之下 终现热忱"
"In the sun, we'll find our passion."
"日光之下 终寻本心"
"In the sun, we will find our purpose."
你一直被悉心保护着 从未真正受过苦
You've always been protected. You've never truly suffered.
这就是我们选择你的原因
And that's why we chose you.
你一直在熟睡
You've always been asleep.
你从未有过机会
You never had a chance.
那个黑发女孩会被关在另一个
The dark-haired girl, she's gonna be kept in another closet
我… 你可能也知道
I... you might as well know at this point.
野兽…
The beast...
就要来抓你们了 来抓你们三个人
He's coming for you. All three of you,
你们会被分开关着
you're gonna be kept separate.
你衣服上沾了一颗面包屑
You've got... you've got a crumb on your shirt.
请你脱下来
Please take it off.
脱下来吧
Just... just take it off.
你说了帕特里夏女士的坏话
It wasn't nice what you said about Ms. Patricia.
你撒谎
You lied.
我很抱歉 黑德维希
I'm sorry about that, Hedwig.
你们骗我 让我害怕之类的
You guys lied to me, made me scare, etc.
丹尼斯先生说你穿了很多衣服
Mr. Dennis, he says you wear a lot of shirts.
我喜欢这件
I like this shirt.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道丹尼斯和帕特里夏女士是什么人吗
Do you know who Dennis and Ms. Patricia are?
不知道
No.
你看 我们所有人都要坐在椅子上等待
See, everyone of us has to wait in a chair.
而巴里来决定谁能表现出来
And Barry, he decides who stand in the light.
但是他因为我丧失了这种权力
But Barry lost that power because of me.
我想什么时候表现 就什么时候表现
I can wish myself in the light anytime I want.
这是我的特殊能力
It's a... it's a special power.
只要我想 巴里就不得不在椅子上坐着
Barry just has to keep sitting in his chair, if I want him to.
所以丹尼斯和帕特里夏女士
That's why Dennis and Ms. Patricia
说我可以跟他们一起待着
said I could be with them.
丹尼斯和帕特里夏女士
Dennis and Ms. Patricia,
他们相信野兽的存在 也相信它的能力
they believe in the beast and what he can do.
你见过他吗
Have you seen him?
野兽
The... beast?
没有 我能吻你吗
No. Can I kiss you?
我想去吻那个黑头发的女孩子
I wanted to kiss the other girl with the dark hair,
但是她现在有麻烦了
but she's in trouble.
你想吗
So you want to?
虽然我也不是很擅长亲吻
I mean, I don't know much about kissing, though.
好的
Yeah.
太好了
Okay.
好的 开始了
Okay, here we go.
我好紧张
I'm so nervous.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
你现在可能已经怀孕了
You might be pregnant now.
- 我的吻技好吗 - 挺好的
- Am I a good kisser? - Yeah.
我喜欢跳舞 你喜欢跳舞吗
I love dancing. You like dancing?
我喜欢在房间里听着CD机的音乐跳舞
I like dancing to my CD player in my room.
我最喜欢听坎耶·维斯特的歌
Kanye West is my main man.
我们在我的房间里放了CD机
We got my CD player set up in my room,
就放在窗户旁边
right next to my window.
我就像这样
I'm like...
"晃动身躯"
"We got the moves!"
或许我可以看着你跳舞
Maybe I could watch you dance
跟你一起听音乐
and listen to music with you.
- 不行 音乐都在我的房间里 - 那好吧
- No, my music is in my room. - Oh, right.
你可以偷偷带我过去
Maybe you could sneak me there.
你是在耍我之类的吗
Are you trying to trick me, etc?
我会告发你的
I'll tell on you.
- 我会告发你的 - 我告诉你一些事情
- I'm telling on you! - I'll tell you something.
你可以判断我是不是在说谎 好吗
And you can tell me if I'm lying or not, okay?
就像是测试一样
Like a test, okay?
我故意在学校惹麻烦
I get into trouble at school on purpose.
这样就可以被留校反省
So I can get sent to detention.
这样我就能远离所有人
To get away from everyone.
我就能一个人呆着
So that I can be alone.
好吧 我带你去看我房间里的东西
Okay, I'll show you something cool in my room.
好的
Okay.
但是要等丹尼斯先生
But after Mr. Dennis
完成典礼的准备工作之后
has finished to getting-ready ritual.
我要走了 他还有个预约
I have to go. He's got an appointment.
我睡着的时候
When I fall sleeping,
他们中总有人想要
one of the others keep trying
去向女医生告发我们
to reach the doctor lady to tell on us.
那条裤子 衬里是红色的
That pant, it's got a red lining.
卡伦·弗莱彻  心理学硕士
从裤子侧边的开口就能看出来
You can see it in the long slit down the side.
我们已经谈了二十分钟的丝绸和羊毛混纺了
We've been talking about silk and wool blend for 20 minutes.
我猜 你大半夜给我发邮件
Well, can I guess that you emailed me in the middle of the night,
要求紧急诊疗
for an emergency session,
应该是有形形色色的问题
due to garden-variety issues?
我不开心 就给你发邮件咯
I was down, and I emailed you.
但是等我醒来的时候 我就好多了
And I woke up and I feel better.
我感觉好多了
I... I feel better.
我有个想法
I had a thought.
我想谈谈工作中发生的事
I want to talk about the incident at work.
没事的 巴里 你很安全
It's okay, Barry. You're safe.
我只是想帮你回忆起一些细节
I just want to bring the details back.
我们只来说说一些细节就好了
We're just talk about the details.
新泽西州卡姆登市的一所高中
A high school from Camden, New Jersey
在你工作的地方举办了一次实习考察
was on a field trip at your place of work.
两个年轻的女生向你走过来
And two young ladies came up to you.
其中一个抓住你的手 放进衬衫里她的胸上
And one took your hand and put it under her shirt on her breast.
另一个也这么做
And the second did the same.
之后她们就跑开了 向她们的朋友们大笑
And then they just run off, laughing to their friends.
你以为她们在玩大冒险的游戏
You surmised that it might be on a dare.
你说过她们大概十七八岁左右
You said they were 17 or 18.
你说因为这件事 你这几天都很失落
You said it upset you for days.
只是个青少年恶作剧罢了 我现在明白了
It was just a teenage prank. I get that now.
你看 这是我的错
And see, that's my mistake.
我觉得这件事我处理得太含糊了
I believe that I went over this incident with you too fast.
虽然你说过你没事
Although you said, you were fine.
而且我见到的其他人格也都说没事
And the other identities I met with said, it was fine.
但是我相信…
I believe that this...
这件事让你想起了童年时受虐的回忆
brought up issues from when you were a child and abused.
有时候 另一个虐待事件
Sometimes another incident of abuse
会使被压抑的人格表现出来
can cause suppressed personalities to take the light.
丹尼斯 如果是你的话
Dennis, if this is you...
我完全理解
I completely understand...
你为什么想掌控身体 保护其他人格
why you felt the need to take over and protect the others.
得了 医生 你又来了
Please. Doctor, not this again.
其他人告诉我 你和帕特里夏
The others told me that you and Patricia
把野兽的事情告诉了大家
told the group about this beast.
而我告诉他们
And I told them that
这些只是丹尼斯和帕特里夏
these are just scary stories
讲给他们听的恐怖故事 是为了吓唬他们
that Dennis and Patricia tell the others, to scare them.
这野兽是如何在墙上爬行
How this beast can crawl on walls,
就像最顶尖的攀岩者
like the best rock climbers
利用最微弱的摩擦力和不平整的地方
using this slightest friction and imperfections,
使身体紧贴几乎垂直的墙面
to hold his body close to seemingly sheer surfaces.
他的皮肤是多么坚硬厚实 就像犀牛的皮
How his skin is thick and tough like the hide of a rhinoceros.
你真的相信这些关于野兽的事吗
Do you really believe the stories about the beast?
如果你是丹尼斯的话
If this is you, Dennis,
我明白为什么凯文需要你了
I understand why Kevin needs you.
你很强壮 又很自律 一丝不苟
You are strong and disciplined. You are precise.
而且你不会让别人利用你
And you will not be taken advantage of.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
比如说 我完全可以利用凯文的全名
For example, I do have the ability to use Kevin's full name
把他叫出来 就像之前那样
and bring him forward, as he has in the past.
但是我不会这么做
But I wouldn't do that.
我知道那会让你们全乱套的
I know that, that would be chaos for all of you.
大家都会想出现
Everyone would grab the light.
我不想那样伤害你们
I don't want to hurt any of you that way.
你不需要躲藏
You don't have to hide.
我知道你是在意凯文的
I know you are someone who cares for Kevin.
我并不觉得你邪恶
You are not evil to me.
你是不可或缺的一部分
You were necessary.
丹尼斯 是你吗
Dennis, is that you?
他们一直把我们大家称为"群"
They keep calling us "the horde".
就是其他的人格
The others, you know.
帕特里夏女士和我 我们被人嘲笑
Ms. Patricia and I, we're ridiculed.
我们的确不完美
Now, we're not perfect.
但也不该被嘲笑
But we don't deserve to be ridiculed.
我们都在抗争 他们必须承认这一点
We're all struggling. They have to admit that.
我很高兴见到你 丹尼斯
I am pleased to meet you, Dennis.
我也是
You, too.
你好像不知道是谁给我发了紧急诊疗的邮件
I assume you don't know who emailed me for the emergency session.
肯定是其他某个人格
One of the others.
- 现在是你主导吗 - 对 是我们了
- Are you in charge? - Yeah, we've taken charge.
只有我们能保护凯文
We're the only ones who can protect Kevin.
我们都是为了保护凯文
We're all here to protect Kevin.
他太软弱
He's very weak.
他不知道我们能有多强大
He doesn't know how powerful we can be.
你能告诉我 你什么时候第一次出现
Would you mind telling me when you first came into existence?
还有你和帕特里夏
And how you and Patricia,
那另一个不受欢迎的人格 是如何结盟的
the other undesirable identity, became aligned?
不说也没关系 你还有坚定的信念吗
That's okay. Do you still have strong beliefs?
- 要看情况 - 这个关于野兽的故事
- That depends on what. - This story of the beast.
丹尼斯 有件事也许能让你不那么迷茫
One thing, Dennis, that may comfort you if you are confused,
你见过其他的人格
is that you've met the other alters.
你们都坐在房间里的椅子上 对吗
You're all in a room in chairs, right?
没错
Yeah.
但你从没见过野兽
But you never met the beast?
因为他不和你们住在一起吗
Because he doesn't reside with the rest of you?
因为他住在铁路场院里
Because he resides in the train yard,
就像故事里说的那样
as the story goes.
因为凯文的父亲是坐火车离开的
Because Kevin's dad left on the train.
但事实是
But the fact is,
你和帕特里夏从没见过野兽
you and Patricia have never met the beast.
- 对吧 - 没有
- Have you? - No.
那是因为他不是一个人格
That's because he's not an alter.
不是第24个
He's not the 24th identity.
他只是你们的幻想
He is a fantasy.
快点 跟我走
Hurry up! Let's go!
过来 是时候了
Come on, it's time!
我知道
I know.
- 那是你的CD机 - 没错
- This is your CD player? - Yeah.
你不喜欢吗 它有年头了
You don't like it? It's not new.
不 不 我只是…
No, no, I'm just a...
我不明白 你说它放在窗户旁边
I'm confused. You said it was near a window.
在这里
Oh, that's here!
看
Watch.
现在是关上的
Now, it's closed.
打开了
Now, it's open.
关上了
Now, it's closed.
打开了
Now, it's open.
你以为是一扇真的窗户吗
Did you think it was a real window?
然后你就能逃走之类的
So you could leave, etc?
帮我逃出去 黑德维希
Help me get out of here, Hedwig.
只要把钥匙给我就好 让我出门
Just give me the keys and let me out the door.
求你了
Please.
帕特里夏女士说
Ms. Patricia says that
等野兽来了 就没人会再嘲笑我了
nobody will make fun of me anymore when the beast comes.
她说所有人都会看到我有多棒
She said that everyone must see how amazing I am.
没有人会在意我那些愚蠢的错误了
And then all of my silly mistakes, they won't matter anymore.
我觉得你应该回你的房间
I think you should go back to your room.
不 等等 求你了
No, wait! Please!
我想听你的坎耶·韦斯特的专辑
I wanna hear your Kanye West albums!
带我去你的房间
Show me your room!
就待在这里吧 抱歉我刚才要离开
Let's stay here, I'm sorry I asked to leave.
我不能
I can't.
你说你要给我看一些酷酷的东西 对吗
You said you wanna show me something cool, right?
- 给我看 - 我不想
- Show me something! - I don't want to!
求你
Please!
这个
This!
- 这很棒 - 这不是个玩具
- It's nice. - It's not a toy.
- 这是真的吗 - 是的
- This this real? - Yes.
是丹尼斯先生的
It's Mr. Dennis'.
他根本不知道我偷了这个
He doesn't even know I stole it.
很酷吧
Pretty cool, right?
你可以听到别人说话
You can listen people talking
而他们根本不知道你在偷听
and they don't even know you're listening.
- 用这个可以和谁通话 - 别碰那里
- Who does this talk to? - Don't touch that.
我只想看看它能不能用
I just want to see if it works.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
别按那个按钮 我们会被发现的
Don't touch the buttons. You're gonna get us found out.
这里是东门 什么事
Yeah, east gate here. What up?
别说话
Do not talk.
怎么了
Whaddup?
- 你好 - 不要
- Hello? - Don't!
我会打你的
I'm gonna slap you!
你是谁
Who is this?
有人在吗 我叫凯茜·库克
Hello? Hello, my name is Casey Cooke!
我被关在了一间地下室里
I'm being held in a basement!
我和其他两个女孩被绑架了
I've been abducted with two other girls!
什么玩意
Who the hell is this?
有人吗
Hello?
凯茜·库克 我被绑架了 你得找到我
Casey Cooke! I've been abducted! You need to find me!
贝蒂 是你吗 这不好玩
Betty, is that you? This isn't fun.
快报警 我肯定离你不远
Call the police! I must be near you.
我被关在一间像地下室的房间里
I'm being held in a basement or something.
行了 贝蒂 帮我向拉里和鱼儿们问好
Okay, Betty, listen. Tell Larry and fish I said hi.
告诉他 他的耳机还在我这儿呢
Tell him I still got his orange earphones and...
我不知道我在哪 这里有个男人
I don't know where I am. There is a man here.
他绑架了我们 他要杀我
He abducted us and he's going to kill me.
我只剩下几个小时了
I only have a few hours left.
求你
Please.
求你了 来人救救我们
I'm begging you. Somebody save us.
等等 你是谁 怎么得到我们的对讲机的
Wait, who is this? And how did you get one of our walkies?
双手合十 摆成忏悔礼
Put your hands together in contrition.
"日光之下 终现热忱"
"In the sun, we will find our passion."
"日光之下 终寻本心"
"In the sun, we will find our purpose."
我在超市的慰问卡上看过这些话
I read that on a sympathy card in the supermarket.
是葬礼用的 但我觉得它很好看
It was for funerals, but I saw it was beautiful.
丹尼斯会向你说明今晚的意义
Dennis will explain the meaning of this evening.
野兽是嗅觉灵敏的生物
The beast is a scenting creature,
代表着人类进化的最高形态
who represents the highest form of human's evolution.
他认为普通人类的时代结束了
He believes the time of ordinary humanity is over.
希望这能让你感到平静
I hope this makes you feel calm.
你将见到更伟大的存在
You will be in the presents of something greater.
我本来要让你脱下最后一件上衣 但不会了
I was gonna ask for your last shirt, but I won't.
因为今晚是神圣的
Because tonight is a sacred night.
快结束了
It's almost over.
凯茜 快点
Casey, come on!
我们再来玩动物扮演游戏吧
Let's pretend we're animals again!
快点
Come on!
凯茜 快 这是我们的游戏
Casey, come on! This is our game!
否则我就告诉你爸 说你不乖
Or I'll tell your dad you're not being nice.
快 把衣服脱光
Come on! Take off your stuff.
动物是不穿衣服的
Animals don't wear clothes.
快点
Come on!
快
凯茜宝贝
Casey-bear.
这不好玩
This isn't funny.
上膛了吗
Is it loaded?
凯茜
Casey?
我是你叔叔
I'm your uncle.
停下 凯茜
Stop it, Casey!
把枪放下
Put that gun down!
我要生气了
I'm getting upset!
我要发火了
I'm about to get very angry!
把枪给我
Give me the gun!
你差点杀了我
You could've killed me.
收件箱 20封未读     巴里: 我们需要你
- 这地方关门了 - 没事的
- This place is closed. - No, it's okay.
- 你进不去的 - 没事
- You can't get in. - No, it's okay.
你好 丹尼斯
Hello, Dennis.
你们中的一位刚给我发了邮件
One of the others emailed me just now.
- 没事吧 - 我们没事
- Is everything okay? - We're fine.
丹尼斯 有你是凯文的福气
Dennis, Kevin is really lucky to have you.
你们很特别 我只是不想你们受伤
You are quite extraordinary. I just don't want you guys get hurt.
你认为我们很特别吗
You think we're extraordinary?
我喜欢你 丹尼斯 我能进去吗
I like you, Dennis. May I come in?
我们可以谈谈吗
And can we talk?
我知道你想告诉我一些事
I know you want to tell me something.
为什么不告诉我呢
Why don't you just tell me?
我们俩很像
We're very similar, you and I.
都是局外旁观者
Both on the outside looking in.
请坐
Please, sit.
很少有人来我家做客 我去给你倒点水
I don't get many visitors. I'll get you some water.
他们在南边那栋楼里给我留了个好地方
They got a proper quarters for me in a building on the south side
但我们都已经搬到这儿了
but we're already here.
他们升我为维修部的主管时
When they promoted me to head of maintenance,
说这里就归我了
they said I could have it.
你要去见谁
Who are you going to meet?
我想谈谈
I want to talk about...
凯文
Kevin and...
还有他母亲对他做的事
what his mother did to him.
我全记得
I remember it all.
我很高兴你突然这么坦白
I'm happy you're suddenly so open.
凯文的妈妈有很多种恶毒的方法
Kevin's mother had rather malevolent ways
来惩罚这个三岁的孩子
of punishing this 3-year-old.
你就是在那时候出现的吗
Is that when you arrived in the light?
是的
Yeah.
避开她注意的一种方式
The one way to avoid her attention
就是让一切保持完美无瑕
was to keep everything spotless, everything perfect.
我知道你的出现是好心 丹尼斯
I know you're coming from good intentions, Dennis,
但现在还有其它方式帮助凯文
but there are other ways to help Kevin now.
我的很多病人进了精神病院
I've lost so many patients into the system.
我想让你知道 丹尼斯
I want you to know, Dennis.
我不会放弃为你们争取的
I will never stop fighting for you.
我的病人已经成了我的家人
My patients have become my family.
我选择了他们 而不是更传统的方式
They are what I've chosen instead of a more traditional path.
我希望你能对我坦白
I hope you feel you can be truly honest with me.
其实我想对你坦白
I actually wanna be honest with you.
我之前撒谎了
I lied before.
你问我有没有见过野兽的时候
When you asked, if I'd ever met the beast,
我说"没见过" 那不是真的
I said "no". That really isn't true.
你写过一个德国女人的事
You wrote about a woman in Germany,
她瞎了十年
who'd been blind for 10 years.
之后被诊断出患了分离性身份识别障碍
And then it was discovered that she had DID.
后来她的三个人格产生了视觉
Then three of her identities developed sight.
你推断 她的视神经再生
You speculated that her optical nerves regenerated
是因为她的信念
because of her beliefs.
你想说什么
What are you trying to say?
弗莱彻医生 有些事情
There are things, Dr. Fletcher,
我们都觉得很难相信
that all of us would find hard to believe.
你是想说 还存在第24个人格吗
Are you trying to tell me there is a 24th identity?
你保护有问题的人
You protect the broken.
你说你认为这个情况很特别时
When you said you saw this situation was extraordinary,
- 我就知道 也许你能理解 - 理解什么
- I knew you can maybe understand. - Understand what?
野兽
The beast...
是真的
is real.
他刚出现 你说中了一切
He's just emerged. You were right about everything.
他长什么样
What does he look like?
他的块头比我大得多
He is much bigger than I am.
而我是我们中块头最大的
And I'm the biggest of all of us.
他很高 很强壮
He's tall, he's very muscular.
他长着长长的鬃毛
He's got a long mane of hair
他的手指是我们的两倍长
and his fingers are... are twice the length of ours.
他相信我们很特别
He believes we're extraordinary.
相信我们并非错误的存在 相信我们的潜能
That we don't represent a mistake, but our potential.
你也是这么说的
You say the same things.
他在行动
He's on the move.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
我不明白 他不可能是真的
I don't understand. He can't be real.
人类的潜能肯定有其极限
There must be limits to what a human being can become.
这个故事还有另一面 对吗
And there's another whole part of the story, isn't there?
以不洁年轻人为食
About the eating of the impure young?
"不洁"到底是什么意思
What does "impure" even mean?
我们应该讨论这个 你才能完全理解
We should discuss that, so that you can understand fully.
- 理解什么 - 有时候
- Understand what? - Sometimes...
没有别的办法
there's just no other way.
你要去见谁
Who are you going to meet?
他
Him.
你知道吗 我想把这些都记下来
You know what, I would love to take notes on all of this.
我们应该在明天诊疗时谈谈这事
We should probably discuss this in a proper session tomorrow.
真的吗 你能接受这事
Really? You're okay with this?
这真是太好了 你非常坦诚
This has been so wonderful, you're being so open.
我可以感受到
I can see that you feel very empowered
野兽的理念让你觉得更强大了
by the philosophies of the beast.
- 我… - 我现在得走了
- I... - I'm going to go now.
我就知道你会理解的 再见
I knew you'd understand. I'll see ya.
你介意
Would you mind...
我借用一下你的洗手间吗
if I used your bathroom?
不介意
No.
就在大厅下面 下楼左手边
It's down the hall, near the stairs on your left.
- 怎么样了 - 好的
- How we doing? - Okay.
你是真的吗
Are you real?
你是谁 救救我
Who is it? Help me.
- 救救我 - 是有人来了吗
- Help me. - Is someone there?
- 我的天呐 - 求你了 救救我
- Oh, my God. - Please, help me!
他们永远达不到自己的潜力
They will never reach their potential.
他们都不重要
They don't really matter.
听我说 丹尼斯
Listen to me, Dennis.
我该更仔细地聆听你的
I should've listened better.
我该知道你能做出什么事来
I should've understood what you're capable of,
你有多强大
how powerful you are.
帕特里夏说你方法行不通
Patricia says your way isn't working.
- 世人现在会理解的 - 丹尼斯
- The world will understand now. - Dennis,
这真是大错特错
this is an egregious wrong.
这些女孩们正在受苦 这是犯罪
These young women are suffering. This is a crime.
我不能让你把她们关在这儿
I can't let you keep them here.
我们得阻止这一切 这个人格很恶毒
We've got to stop this. This identity is monstrous.
你这样觉得 我很抱歉
I'm really sad you feel this way.
你不明白吗
Can't you see?
就是因为你在这里待着 他才形成了
He is formed because of your time in this place.
刚刚有位女士
There's a lady.
有人来了
Someone's here!
我们得逃出去
We need to get out of these rooms!
房间里有什么东西吗 任何我们能用的东西
Is there anything in the room? Anything that we could use?
什么也没有
There's nothing in here.
这儿有个钩子
There is a hanger.
谢谢你 丹尼斯
Thank you, Dennis.
给您 先生
Here you go, sir.
刚才听起来
It sounded like there were slide bolts
我们门外应该是滑闩
on the outside of our doors.
你试试看能不能通过门的缝隙把锁打开
See if you can move the lock through the crack in the door.
网络无法连接
保持冷静 我们能出去的
Stay calm. We're getting out of here.
我们能找到凯茜
We're gonna get Casey.
你能做到 玛西亚
You can do this, Marcia.
1_巴里  2_杰德  3_奥威尔
3_ 奥威尔
印度历史
就像是卡哈马那王朝[7世纪-12世纪]被打败
It's regarded to Chahamana's defeat
以及古尔的穆罕默德从1192到1200年间的征服
and Muhammad of Ghor's conquests between 1192 and 1200.
我想把它比作穆罕穆德厚颜无耻的最后通牒
I would liken it to Muhammad's brazen ultimatum,
普利维拉"要么放弃信仰要么战斗"
that Prithviraj "either apostatize or fight".
就像普利维拉的反抗
Like Prithviraj's defiance...
面对"群"的进攻 我们应该奋起反抗
we should stand up to the horde's advances.
面对他们的恐吓战术 我们应该表现出
In the face of their scare tactics, we should show...
2_杰德
我恨胰岛素注射
I hate my insulin shots.
这里其他人都不需要注射胰岛素
No one else around here has to take them.
为什么就我有糖尿病
Why do I have to have diabetes?
所有的医生 包括弗莱彻医生
All the doctors, besides Dr. Fletcher,
都说我们就是一个人的不同人格
say that we're the same person, just personalities.
那你怎么解释只有我需要这破玩意儿
How do you explain I'm the only one that needs this?
你个狗娘养的
You motherfu...
1_巴里
我穿着九十年代的工装裤
I'm wearing cargo pants from the 90s.
还有条围巾
And a scarf.
如果不是里面穿着名设计师的T恤
If it wasn't for the Varvatos T-shirt underneath,
那我就丑死了
I'd be a mess.
我现在一点品味都没有了
I got no taste for things right now.
我很担心
I'm worried sick.
我有着失去时间的不祥预感
I have a very bad feeling that I'm losing time.
我能决定谁得到表现机会 不是吗
I decide who gets the light, right?
有人正趁我不注意 偷走我的表现机会
I think someone is stealing the light from me when I'm not aware.
"群"一直执着于那些没受过苦的人
The horde keeps obsessing about the ones who haven't suffered.
我不知道他们这样下去会怎样
I don't know where they're going with this,
但我感到很害怕
but it scares me.
想象着再过几个小时你就在家了
Picture yourself in a couple hours at home.
窝在沙发里
On the couch,
穿着你喜欢的那件丑汗衫
in that ugly-ass sweatshirt that you love.
那是只动物
It's an animal.
他叫得好像遇到了土狼之类的似的
He goes like this if there's a coyote or something.
凯文 凯文 凯文
Kev... Kev... Kev...
凯文
Kev...
谢谢你
Thank you
一直以来的帮助
for helping us till now.
凯文 凯文
Kev... Kev...
我想我该告诉弗莱彻医生
I guess I should tell Dr. Fletcher about this, but...
但她会担心的 她是个大好人
She'll worry. She is such a sweet woman.
我应该去好好散个步
I believe I will go for a nice walk
系统地想想这件事
and think this through organizationally.
这就是我周一的日记
Thus ends my journal for Monday.
再见
Ciao.
克莱尔
Claire?
玛西亚
Marcia?
克莱尔 克莱尔我们快走
Claire! Claire, let's go!
凯文·温德尔·克拉姆
Kevin Wendell Crumb?
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
凯文·温德尔·克拉姆
Kevin Wendell Crumb!
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
凯文·温德尔·克拉姆
你闯祸了
You made a mess.
滚出来
Come out here.
凯文·温德尔·克拉姆 你闯祸了
Kevin Wendell Crumb! You made a mess!
滚出来
Get out there!
你是谁 发生了什么
Who are you? Wha... what's happening?
一些可怕的事情
Something horrible.
我做了什么
What'd I do?
我伤害你了吗
Did I hurt you?
弗莱彻医生 弗莱彻医生
Dr. Fletcher. Dr. Fletcher!
这是谁干的
Who did that?
你干的
You did.
我发誓 我正在公车上
I swear I was on a bus.
之后什么事我都不记得了 我
I don't remember anything after that. I...
现在还是2014年9月18号 是吗
This is still September 18, 2014, right?
我买了一支猎枪
There's a shotgun I bought.
就在一堆杂物后面最底下的柜子里
It's in the bottom cabinet, hidden behind things.
子弹在供电间里的我的制服柜里
The shells are in my uniform closet, out in the service wall.
杀了我
Kill me.
然后杀了我
Then kill me.
等一下等一下 不要这么做
Wait, wait, wait! No, no, don't do that!
他无法面对现实
He can't handle reality.
我叫杰德
My name is Jade.
弗莱彻医生收到我们的邮件了吗
Has Dr. Fletcher been getting our emails?
我们必须要这样做 我们可以…
This is what we have to do. We can...
喀布尔-夏希王朝历史
该王朝位于现今阿富汗和巴基斯坦一带
在1008年
As in 1008,
当安纳达佩拉惨遭夏希王朝最毁灭性的战败
when Anandapala suffered the shahis' most crushing defeat
而默罕默德统治了整个旁遮普
and Mahmud overran the entirety of the Punjab Region,
占领了著名康格拉神庙的时候
taking the famed Temple of Kangra,
我们被"群"错怪了
we have been wronged by this alliance,
帕特里夏 丹尼斯还有那个男孩
this horde of Patricia, Dennis and the boy.
他们的行为不代表我们
Their actions do not represent us!
他们…
They... are every...
你们大家都冷静一下
Everybody, just take a minute!
小姑娘…
Baby girl...
他们一直都从我手里偷走表现机会
They've been stealing control of the light from me,
但我们团队会解决这个问题的
but the group are gonna work through this.
亲爱的 我叫巴里
Honey, my name is Barry.
你不该用那个对讲机的
You shouldn't have used the walkie-talkies.
他们差点就抓住我们了
They almost caught us.
别这样 黑德维希
Stop it, Hedwig!
他们说得对
They were right.
看看你 你多害怕我们啊
Look at you! You're so frightened of us.
丹尼斯和帕特里夏女士是因为我才能得到控制权的
Dennis and Ms. Patricia are in charge because of me!
我现在要把表现机会给他们了
I'm gonna give the light to them now.
再没有人能够嘲笑我了
No one's allowed to make fun of me anymore!
谢谢你 黑德维希
Thank you, Hedwig.
现在没事了
Everything's fine now.
凯文·温德尔·克拉姆
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
凯文睡着了 我们让他在很远处睡着了
Kevin is asleep. We've made him sleep far away.
你想叫他就叫吧 亲爱的 但…
You can call his name all you like, dear, but...
他听不到你说话的
he's not going to hear you.
野兽给我们看了他的梦想
The beast has shared with us his dream
想要有更多人来维持他的存在
of a larger group to sustain him.
不
No!
下一次就用十到二十个没用的年轻人
Ten to twelve unworthy young next time.
不 不
No, no...
这仅仅是开始
This is just the start!
克拉姆
放开我
Let go!
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
救命
Help!
救命 救命 救命
Help! Help! Help!
不
No.
这是家族遗传的
It runs in our family.
我爸爸也去世了
My daddy died, too.
也是这样 心脏病发
Same way, heart attack.
不过你不用担心 我会好好照顾你的
But you don't need to worry. I'm going to take care of you.
你不会给我惹什么麻烦的 对吧
Now, you won't be giving me any trouble, will you?
我知道你不会的 宝贝
I know you won't, sweetie.
我们真是太美了
We are glorious!
我们不再会害怕了
We will no longer be afraid!
只有通过痛苦
Only through pain...
你才能实现自身的伟大
can you achieve your greatness!
纯洁者是未被染指
The impure are the untouched,
未受火侵 未被杀害的
the unburned, the unslain!
那些没受过折磨的人
Those who have not been torn,
自身没什么意义
have no value in themselves
在这世上也无立足之地
and no place in this world!
他们都睡着了
They are asleep!
你的枪伤不了我
Your gun cannot hurt me.
你看不出来吗 我不是人类
Can't you see? I am not human.
凯文是个人类 我比他强多了
Kevin is a man. I am much more.
你和其他人不一样
You... you are different from the rest.
你的心是纯洁的
Your heart is pure.
太棒了
Rejoice!
受过伤的人才更高等
The broken are the more evolved!
太棒了
Rejoice!
我的老天爷啊
What in the name of Mary Joseph!
你在这里干什么
What are you doing in this area?
继续走 宝贝 它们不会伤害你的
Just keep walking, honey. They won't do nothing.
文斯 报警
Vince, call the police!
她说在下面维修区有人受伤了
She said some people got hurt in the area below maintenance.
好了
Okay.
我给你检查一下
Now, I'm just gonna check you.
黑德维希
第三名死者为卡伦·弗莱彻医生
Third deceased-- name of Dr. Karen Fletcher.
我们还在联系她的家人
Still trying to locate the family.
凯茜·库克斯的监护人到了
Casey Cooke's guardian's here.
你叔叔来了
You uncle's here.
准备好走了吗
You ready to go?
没成功
It didn't go through.
我们相信自己是什么就是什么
We are what we believe we are.
天哪 这也太帅了
Holy shit! This is so cool!
现在他们相信我们存在了吧
They're gonna believe we exist now, right?
他们必须得相信
They're gotta have to.
那我们现在该怎么办
So what are we do now?
我们相信他
We trust in him.
他会保护我们的
He'll protect us.
看看他的能耐
Look at what he can do.
让他告诉这个世界看看我们能有多强大
Let him show the world how powerful we can be.
分裂
嫌疑凶手 凯文·克拉姆 患有一种
The suspected murderer, Kevin Crumb,
富有争议的心理疾病 分裂型人格障碍
suffers from the controversial psychological disorder, DID.
现场传言简直令人难以置信
The rumors coming out of the scene are almost unbelievable.
人们对于嫌疑人近距离挨了两枪以后
There are conflicting stories if the suspect is alive or dead
是生是死还不确定
after sustaining two point-blank gunshots.
报道甚至称 他其中一个人格
Reports even indicate one of his personalities
是一系列动物的混合体
is an amalgam of various animals
就是他工作过的费城动物园里的动物
in the Philadelphia Zoo, where he worked.
媒体已经开始用
The press is already referring
知情者透露的一个暗号
to the alleged attacker by a dark name,
来代指这位受指控的袭击者
leaked by a source close to the case.
因为他的多重人格
Because of his many personalities,
他被称为"群"
he is being called "the horde".
这就像那个15年前被关起来的那个奇怪的
This is like that crazy guy in the wheelchair
坐轮椅的人一样
that they put away 15 years ago.
他们给他也取了个奇怪的名字
And they gave him a funny name, too.
叫什么来着
What was it?
- 玻璃先生 - 对
- Mr. Glass. - Oh, yeah.